

Nguyễn Hữu Tường

Front-End Developer

Phone: +84 7666 93571

Email: nguyenhuutuong999@gmail.com

Skype: nguyenhuutuong999 Address: Da Nang, Viet Nam

Summary

Hi, I'm Tuong. I have over 3 years of experience working with the Framework/Library of JavaScript (ReactJS, VueJS). I'm considered a good team player because I would like to help others and tend to work well within a group. From that, I will contribute to the development of the company.

In the future, I would like to learn about Front-End more and become a Full-Stack developer in the long term. My focus is on trying to learn as much as possible and doing my best in order to accomplish assigned tasks, supporting my team members, researching, and applying new technologies effectively, which gives me the motivation to fulfill my potential.

Technical Skill

lα	n	a	u	a	a	es

Javascript, Typescript HTML, CSS C#

Version Control

Git (Github & Bitbucket, Gitlab)

Frameworks/Libraries

ReactJS, NextJS, VueJS NodeJS React Native

Foreign Languages

TOEIC: 600/900 (Mock Test) Speaking Skill: Good

Database MS

SQL Server, MySQL Firebase MongoDB

Soft Skill

Time Management Teamwork Research

Education

Duy Tan University (Full scholarship)

Aug 2017 - Aug 2021 Information System Management

GPA: 3.59/4.0

Jun 2018 Top 5 Excellent Students Scholarship of BAP

Company in the first year

Reference

Jun 2021 Best Graduation Project

Reference

Jul 2021 Top 2 Scientific Research of School

Reference

Certification

Mar 2019 Responsive Web Design of FreeCodeCamp

Reference

Work Experience

NashTech Global Company

Nov 2021-Now

Warehouse Mamagement System (Japan)

The logistic management system improves inventory performance with procurement rules depending on stock levels, logistic rules, and sales orders....

Role (Front-End Developer):

- Developed Authentication, Authorization
- Developed: Stock, Supplier, Customer, Billing, Import Excel, and File Management

Tech: ReactJS, Ant Design, il8n, Java

Orient Software Company

Nov 2020 - Nov 2021

Marketplacer (Australia)

The Marketplacer that is platform gives Enterprise Companies the agility to scale and grow in today's evolving e-commerce environment.

Role (React Developer):

- Developed search, filter, and product details.
- Write Unit Test and Integration test by Jest

Tech: ReactJS, NextJS, Rails, GraphQL, Lambda Function

July 2020 - Nov 2020

SWINGWORK (Germany)

A website with a landing page and a web application related to playing golf, connecting golf players from novices to professionals.

Role (Full-Stack Developer):

- Developed: Register Course, Manage Golf Club, Time Zone
- Maintenance

Tech: ReactJS, Net Core

Mar 2020 - July 2020

HR Assist

A web application for HR to manage the company's employee, team, and project easily instead of doing it with Excel.

Role (Full-Stack Developer):

- Design Database
- Developed Export, Filter, and Team Member Management
- Developed Restful API by .Net Core

Tech: VueJS, Vuex, Vue Material, Net Core

Jan 2020 - Mar 2020

Scrum Base

This is an internal project in which the app helps people manage a project by Scrum methodology (similar to Trello).

Role (React Native Developer):

• Developed Login, Task, and Project Management

Tech: ReactJS, React Native, Redux, Redux-Thunk